Previously on Haven...
前情提要
This is Nathan. He's the "way to my heart" guy.
这是Nathan 他就是我心里那个人
When I cut his head open, I found this.
我开了他的颅 发现了这个
- That was in his brain? - Yep.
- 这玩意在他脑子里? - 嗯
You... this whole day, the black goo, all the delusions...
是你...这一整天 这个黑团 所有的幻觉...
you infected my friends, and you put that mark on those people.
是你感染了我的朋友们 是你在那些人身上做了记号
I'm just trying to get through to you.
我只是想要找回你
- You're immune to The Troubles. - Just like you.
- 你对异能免疫 - 跟你一样
I want you back.
我想要你回来
Find the Troubled person, or the hansons die.
找出异能者 否则我就杀了Hansen一家人
I wouldn't help you, not in this world or any other.
我不会帮你的 不管在这个世界还是别的世界
Yeah, you will, 'cause if you don't, more people are gonna die...
你当然会的 如果你不帮我 有更多人会死
and people that Audrey Parker cares about.
都是Audrey Parker在意的人
William can't get away with this. I didn't come here to talk.
不能让William脱罪 我来不是为了跟你谈判的
So I'm gonna tell you everything you want to know
所以你们想知道她是谁 我们一起做过什么
about who she is and what we did, 'cause we are so connected.
这些我都告诉你们 因为我们俩是相连的
Got the logo, coming around the van, and action.
拍到标识 绕过车 然后开拍
Greetings, Seekers. Welcome to Haven, Maine.
大家好 寻鬼者们 欢迎来到缅因州的港湾镇
As always, I'm Seth byrne, joined by my steady hand behind the camera, Anderson Harris.
我是Seth Byrne 还有史上手最稳的摄像 我的搭档Anderson Harris
And we are The Darkside Seekers.
我们是暗黑寻鬼者
Say hello, Anderson.
打个招呼 Anderson
Hello, Seekers. It is I, Anderson Harris.
好啊 寻鬼者们 本大爷Anderson Harris
Welcome to hell.
欢迎来到地狱
- That's a weird voice, dude. - Thanks, buddy.
- 这声音真诡异 哥们儿 - 谢啦兄弟
We'll cut it out.
得剪掉
We've come to Haven to investigate a murder.
我们来港湾调查谋杀案
The victim was found missing his heart.
死者丢失了他的心脏
Think that's strange? Well, we thought so too.
奇怪吧? 我们也这么觉得
Ooh. Easy, there, big guy. Walking's tough, huh?
哎呀 小心点 老大 走个路也这么费劲啊?
This is a new shirt, so that sucks.
这可是新衣服 真糟心
Well, that's gonna smell good.
哈 这绝对够味儿
Okay, let's take it from the top.
从头开始吧
No, no, we're fine. I can cut around it.
不用 没事 我能剪掉这段
- Yeah? - Yeah, man.
- 是吗? - 当然了兄弟
- Yeah? Okay. - The magic of editing.
- 是吗? 那好吧 - 编辑的魔力
All right, well, your mustache looks good. You ready?
行了 你的胡子挺帅的 准备好了吗?
- Yeah. - Clean. Ready?
- 嗯 - 好了 准备好了吗?
- Yeah. Hold on. - Three, two...
- 嗯 等等 - 三 二...
And... Action.
预备...开拍
This isn't the first strange thing we've heard about Haven.
我们听说港湾出的怪事可不止这一桩
If you know where to look, Haven is home to all kinds of paranormal activity,
如果你知道去哪里找 港湾可四处潜藏着各种超自然现象
like haunted houses or shape-shifters, maybe even a golem.
比如鬼屋 变形怪 甚至石魔
But the law enforcement here, with help from the local daily rag, cover it up.
但当地警方在当地报社的帮助下 掩盖了事实真相
They say, "it was a freak accident,"
他们总说 "这是一起诡异的事故"
or maybe insect migration.
或者昆虫迁移
Or... this is my personal favorite... a gas leak.
或者...我个人最喜欢这个借口 气体泄漏
I mean, a gas leak? I mean, what?
气体泄漏? 谁信啊?
How many gas leaks does a small fishing village need to have
一个小渔村能搞出几次气体泄漏啊?
before they get new pipes?
他们连新管道都不知道什么时候换
Is something a man might wonder.
这个事情就很可疑了
Recently we've been receiving strange readings from our devices,
最近我们的仪器一直收到奇怪的读数
which have led us to this house, where we hope to find clues to...
它们把我们引到了这栋房子 希望我们能在这里找到线索...
What the hell was that? Is there something in there?
什么情况? 这里面有东西吗?
Dude, look, look, look. Come on.
哥们 快看 跟我来
- Is the door open? - Come on, come on, come on.
- 那门开着吗? - 快来 快来
- Please, come on. - Seth, do not go inside there.
- 快点来啦 - Seth 别进去
- Dude, we are going inside. - I'm not going inside there.
- 咱一定得进去 - 我才不要进去
Dude, you are going in.
你非得进去
The door is ripped off.
门直接被拆下来的
Don't go in there.
可别进去啊
Oh, my God, dude, turn that off, please.
天啊 哥们 快关掉
??????????
快把这仪器关掉
- This thing actually works? - Yeah. Duh
- 这东西还真有用啊? - 废话
Wait. Hang on. It's too dark.
等等 太黑了
I can't see anything. Let me adjust the camera.
什么都看不到 让我调整一下摄像机
Oh, for God sakes, just hurry up.
老天啊 你可快点吧
- We want to find this. - Okay, okay.
- 千万别错过要找的东西 - 知道了 知道了
Jeez. Really?
天哪 真的假的?
Can... can we get a shot of this?
能拍一下这个吗?
Look at the... look at the space between the talons here, right?
你快看这爪子的间距
I'm guessing this thing is about ten feet.
这东西怎么也得有十英尺高
And based on what we know about its feeding habits... oh, God.
根据它已知的进食习惯...天哪
What happened here?
这里发生过什么事?
Look at this.
快看这个
Is that the lady's blood?
这是那位女士的血吗?
Yeah, I know, I know, I know. Just quiet, okay?
哎呀我知道了 闭嘴行吗?
Don't go in there.
你别进去啊
I'm gonna go in there... 'Cause I have to go in there.
我要进去 我必须要进去
- Get out! - What?
- 快出去! - 啊?
Go! Just go!
快! 赶紧走!
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 港湾 第四季第11集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 港湾 第四季第11集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：茶泡饭
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：萝卜头 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：茶泡饭
So what do you think?
你怎么想?
Well, it'd be a cute rental if it wasn't totally wrecked...
要不是被毁得够彻底 这地方还行
claw marks, smashed TV, the whole "bull in the China shop" motif.
到处都是爪印 电视被砸烂了 颇有种公牛闯进瓷器店的感觉
- About the victim, Gloria. - Abby banks...schoolteacher, and from the looks of the rug,
- 我是说死者 Gloria - Abby Banks 教师 从地毯上撒的东西看
she just finished eating dinner... chicken tikka masala.
她刚吃过晚饭 咖喱鸡块
Can we focus on what's still in the victim?
能不能先说一下死者本身的问题?
Yeah, well, funny you should bring that up.
好吧 这话不用你说
Okay, so we've got claw and bite marks here, there...
这里有爪痕齿痕 那边也有
This is what spilled the dinner, but that's not what killed her.
所以才打翻晚饭的 但这个不是死因
Just like the last one we found, this Vic's heart is gone,
跟上一个受害者一样 死者的心脏没有了
like it was eaten right out of her chest.
像是被人挖出来吃了
"Eaten"?
"吃了"?
Yeah, well, they look like teeth marks to me.
是 我咋看这些都像是齿痕
Anyway, whatever this trouble is, it's big and mean, and it's...
总之 不管这次是什么异能吧 都是大型凶残且...
Don't be shushing me, silverback.
少嘘我 你个大猩猩
Look.
你看啊
Well, what do you know?
哎呀 这谁能想到呢?
Another body found with its heart eaten.
又一具心脏被吃掉的尸体
Pair that with what we saw last night,
对比我们昨晚看到的情形
and, Seekers, it looks like we found ourselves a rougarou.
各位寻鬼者们 咱们貌似是发现了一只食肉怪
Oh, I don't think that's how you say that.
我怎么觉着人不叫这名字
Dude, can I... do you mind if I just do this?
你能让我把话说完么?
Ready. And action.
准备好了吗 开拍
A rougarou is a supernatural creature out of ancient folklore.
食肉怪是远古传说中的超自然生物
A cousin of the werewolf, rougarous were once men,
作为狼人的近亲 食肉怪曾经也是人类
but are now monsters, driven to feed on the hearts of their victims.
但后来变成了怪物 以心脏为食
What about the stuff she was saying to officer Bigfoot about Troubles?
那女的跟大脚怪警察说的异能是什么东西?
What are The Troubles?
异能是什么?
Great question, Anderson. I don't know.
问得好 Anderson 我也不知道
But it's obvious that they're trying to hide something from the outside world.
但很明显 他们向外界隐瞒了一些事情
And as Seekers, it's our job to find out.
作为寻鬼者 我们的使命就是找出真相
Find out what? You can't be recording. This is an ongoing police investigation.
找什么真相? 不准录影 这是正在调查中的案件
- You're ruining the shot, dude. - You want to end up on wikileaks, huh?
- 我这儿正拍着呢 全让你毁了 大哥 - 你是想上维基泄密吗?
What about the claw marks? Why are you suppressing the truth?
爪印怎么说? 你们为什么要压制真相?
- Turn off the camera. - Do not turn off that camera.
- 关掉摄像机 - 别关掉摄像机
This is a public thoroughfare. We can record what we want.
这是公路 我们想怎么录就怎么录
Since when is there no freedom of the press in Maine, huh?
缅因州什么时候起没有媒体自由了?
- What are you, some kind of a fascist? - What are you, a fascist?
- 你是什么啊 法西斯吗? - 你是法西斯吗?
I wish there was something more I could do for Audrey.
真希望我能做点什么帮助Audrey
Actually, there may be something you can do.
可能还真有你能帮得上忙的事情
If anybody knows about this connection between Audrey and William, it's Vince and Dave.
如果有人了解Audrey和William之间的连接 那肯定是Vince和Dave了
How would you feel about going back to the herald and...
你愿不愿意回先驱报上班
Doing the journalist thing, seeing if you can find anything out.
继续当记者 看能不能查出什么来
- Okay. What are you gonna do? - Help Nathan.
- 好的 那你干什么呢? - 帮Nathan
He's torn up about Audrey, and I just...
因为Audrey的事 他心都碎了
I think he's gonna need someone backing him up...
我觉得他可能需要有人支持他
Even if I'm not as cute as his regular partner.
虽说我没他平时的搭档长得好看吧
I disagree.
这我可不同意
- Be safe. - Okay. See you soon.
- 注意安全啊 - 好的 回见
The bullet missed major organs,
子弹没有打中主要器官
but I am not buying that you just dug it out.
但我不信你把它给挖出来了
- Is it in there? - Better if it were.
- 它在里面吗? - 在就好了
Could help staunch blood flow, like it's doing for that guy,
还能帮忙止血 就像那个家伙一样
who, save for the bullet, has the exact same wound. Hmm. Weird.
- 被子弹救了一命 伤口刚好跟她的在一样的位置 - 真奇怪
Okay. I'll start getting an O.R. ready.
好吧 我去准备手术室了
What happened?
怎么回事?
William kept saying that we were connected.
William一直在说我俩是相连的
I guess it's real... Physically.
还真是...身体相连的
Look, if hurting him is gonna hurt Audrey,
如果伤害他就等于伤害Audrey
that is gonna make him very hard to deal with.
那还真没法处理这家伙了
How long can we keep William sedated?
我们能让William昏过去多久?
I say we dope him up forever.
要我说 让他彻底昏死过去算了
I'll stick the needles in myself.
我自己亲自给他扎针
Thanks.
谢啦
Audrey, how are you?
Audrey 你还好吧?
- She's gonna be fine. - Oh, thank God.
- 她会没事的 - 感谢上帝
Nathan, we need you.
Nathan 我们需要你
Another person has been killed... heart gone.
又死人了 心脏不见了
It's a trouble.
是异能
When isn't it?
啥时候不是了?
That's not all.
不止这一件事
Some ghost chasers have come to Haven.
有两个寻鬼者跑港湾来了
So what? Chase them off.
那又咋了? 赶出去呗
You know how to deal with outsiders.
你又不是不知道该怎么处理外人
Too late. They've hacked into the herald's computers,
太晚了 他们黑进了先驱报的电脑
and they now know about the heart eater.
知道食心者的事儿了
They're calling it a rougarou.
他们叫它食肉怪
- But if they chase down their monster,they'll find a Troubled person. - Okay, okay.
- 万一他们找到所谓的怪物 就会发现其实是异能者 - 哎呀 行啦
We've all seen real Bigfoot housewives.
谁还没看过这种神神叨叨的节目
Nobody takes these conspiracy guys seriously.
没人会把这种阴谋论的家伙说的话当真的
But these Troubles are real.
可异能是真的啊
And if these darkside Seekers find some evidence...
如果这两个暗黑寻鬼者找到什么证据...
Then every government agency we know of, and some we don't, will be here,
那我们知道或不知道的政府部门就都要冒出来了
getting in the way of a deadly trouble.
我们处理异能的时候 专门跑这儿来添乱
That's right.
对
Nathan, you can't do the surgery.
Nathan 你守在这儿也没用
So why don't you and Duke go solve this trouble?
所以你跟Duke去解决异能吧
Make sure it doesn't kill anyone else.
确保它别再伤人了
That way, they won't have anything else to chase.
这样他俩也就没什么可追踪的了
Please. Do it for me.
去吧 就当是为了我
Come on.
走吧
How are you really feeling?
你现在感觉到底怎样?
You know me better than I know myself.
你比我还要了解我自己
Please, do you know anything about William?
求你了 告诉我你知不知道William的事?
We don't, I swear.
我们真不知道 我发誓
This is uncharted territory for all of us.
这是我们所有人都未知的领域
William kept saying that we're connected, even more than this gunshot wound.
William一直在说我俩是相连的 不仅仅是这个枪伤的问题
And when we were up on the hill... I felt it.
我们当时在小山上的时候 我感觉到了
There is something there.
确实有什么东西
And it terrifies me.
吓到我了
Audrey, what is it?
Audrey 是什么?
William said that he and I are responsible for The Troubles.
William说 异能这事要怪我和他
They're here because of us, because of me.
异能都是我们弄出来的 都怪我
No. I can't believe that.
不 我不相信
I don't want to believe it either, but there's a part of me that...
我也不愿意相信 可我心底有个声音告诉我
Thinks he might be telling the truth.
他说的可能是真的
- Have you told Nathan? - No.
- 你告诉Nathan了吗? - 没有
No.
没有
Her name's jemma Greene... renovates commercial properties, best friends with our last victim.
她叫Jemma Greene 翻修商用地产的 是上一位死者的闺蜜
Phone records show she was talking to Abby just before the attack.
电话记录显示袭击发生前她正在和Abby通话
We'd been best friends since the day we were born.
我俩是发小 是最好的朋友
I just can't believe someone would do that to her.
我真不敢相信有人会对她做出这种事来
Someone or something?
是有人还是有什么东西?
Hey, you two, out.
你们俩 滚出去
This is an active police investigation.
这是正在调查中的案件
Hey, you guys, smile for the camera while you're oppressing our rights.
压迫我们权利的法西斯 来对着镜头笑一个
And arresting you? Okay, I will.
顺便逮捕你们? 好啊没问题
Calm down. Okay?
别激动 行吗?
Look, I don't think anybody's gonna have to get arrested
我们没打算逮捕谁
because that camera looks broken to me.
因为我觉着那个摄像机好像是坏的
Oh, you playing bad cop today, ponytail?
怎么 今天由你来扮演坏警察啊 马尾辫?
Just keep rolling. He can't arrest us.
接着拍 他才抓不了我们呢
Yeah, I know he can't arrest us, which is why I'm gonna keep exercising
我当然知道他不能抓我们 所以我才要继续实行第一修正案
my first-amendment right of free speech and ask you, Mr. ponytail,
赋予我自由发言的权利 马尾辫先生
don't you feel like grunge died in the '90s?
您这头型90年代就不流行了吧?
Really? I'm trying to be nice to you.
你不是吧? 我是想友好一点
- I'm just trying to be nice to you. - Okay, I'm gonna kick his ass now.
- 我是想友好一点 - 让我揍扁这个混蛋
Give me that camera. Give me that camera!
把摄像机给我 摄像机给我!
Give me that camera!
快把摄像机给我!
- okay - ????
- 好了 - 食肉怪来了?
Don't shoot anymore. It's not rolling.
别开枪 我没拍
Everyone just stay calm, try to be quiet.
大家都别激动 安静下来
- Okay, okay, okay. - Let's get out the back.
- 好了 好了 - 咱们到后面去
- I'll take the lead. Duke, here... - Thanks.
- 我走前面 Duke 给 - 谢谢
- Ready? - Yeah.
- 准备好了吗? - 好了
Let's get out the back. I like this plan.
咱们去后面吧 真喜欢这个计划
I'll follow you. Go, go, go.
我跟着你 走 快走
Let's go.
快点走
Wait, wait.
等等 等等
Wait. I think it's gone.
等会儿 我觉得它走了
Are you sure?
确定吗?
Okay. Let's get out of here.
好 那我们赶紧离开这里
Go, go, go, go, go.
快走 走吧
- What is that? - Where is it? Where is it?
- 那是啥啊? - 哪里? 哪里?
- What is it? - Shh, shh, shh.
- 嘘 嘘
Get down. Get down.
趴下 趴下
Go! Go!
走! 快走!
- Oh, my God! - Keep going!
- 老天啊! - 赶紧走!
Come on! Come on!
快点! 快点!
Get down! Get down!
蹲下! 蹲下!
Where the hell is it?
那东西到底在哪?
All right, all right, we got to go.
行了 我们得走了
Come on, let's go. That way.
好了 走吧 走这边
It's okay.
没事了
Jemma, where are you?
Jemma 你在哪?
Nathan! Nathan!
Nathan! Nathan!
- Where's jemma? - She was with you.
- Jemma在哪? - 她跟你在一起啊
I lost her.
没看住
Nathan, I think I found the breaker box.
Nathan 我找到电路箱了
There she is.
她在那边
What was that?
刚才那是什么?
Call it in. I'll see what else I can find.
快上报 我看看还能找到其他什么线索
You two all right?
你俩没事吧?
Is she dead?
她死了吗?
You record any of it?
你们录下什么了没?
no. I, uh...
没有 我...
I was so scared, I'm... Lucky I didn't break the camera.
我吓坏了 我... 没摔坏摄像机就不错了
Right.
好吧
That was crazy. I mean, that thing just went right for her.
我靠啊 那玩意直冲着她去的
And when we got separated, I just... I just panicked.
我们分开以后 我...我真的吓坏了
Hey, Seth.
嘿 Seth
- Yeah. - Take a look at this.
- 嗯? - 过来看看这个
Wait. You got it?
等下 你居然录到了?
Damn right. I was up and running.
废话 咱是谁啊
Look at that thing.
你看这东西
We got it on camera.
我们拍到了
- So this arugula... - Rougarou.
- 这只尸肉怪... - 是食肉怪
And we don't know that.
我们还不确定它就是了
Well, what we do know is what it wants, and that is hearts.
至少我们知道它想要心脏
These other wounds like the gashed forearm,
其他伤口 像手臂划伤啊
the missing fingers... they're just defensive.
指头掉了之类的 都是防御伤口
Why the heart?
为什么要心脏?
That's your job, detective. I just figure out the what.
那是你的工作 警探 我只负责搞清楚情况
The why... that's up to you and, uh, your honorary deputy over there.
原因得归你和你那位荣誉警官查才对
I actually prefer consulting detective.
我更喜欢被叫做顾问侦探
Oh, a Sherlock fan.
哎哟 喜欢福尔摩斯啊
Well, what does your deductive reasoning make of this?
那你给咱演绎推理一下这个是啥?
Traces found in all the victims.
所有死者身上都有这个痕迹
- I'm gonna go with blood, Bob. - Well, you'd be 90% right.
- 我估计可能是血 Bob - 有90%是对的吧
But there's other stuff mixed in there, and I'm trying to separate it out with a centrifuge.
但是还有东西混在里面 我打算用离心机分离出来
It's thicker than blood, sticky... maybe saliva?
比血重 比较黏 是不是唾液?
I don't know, but it's from the Troubled person...
不知道 但这是异能者身上的
Which is why I've already put him for a rush on the DNA test.
所以我已经拿去做加急DNA测试了
Thank you, Gloria.
谢谢你 Gloria
Got it.
客气
- The people have a right... - Those little twerps.
- 人们有权知道... - 这俩王八蛋
I will handle this. You'd just make things worse. Meet me at the station.
我来处理吧 你只会把事情搞得更糟 到警局等我
I wasn't gonna do anything.
我当时没打算抽他们
You want to see something cool?
想不想看点很酷的东西?
So where's the freedom fighter... out seeking the truth?
那个自由战士呢? 出去寻找真相了吗?
- Thai food... he gets hungry. - What do you want?
- 去吃泰国菜了 他饿了 - 你们想干嘛?
Look, I saw the thing. I know the truth.
我看到那个东西了 我知道真相
I know what you're covering up in there. And hold on a second. People, man...
我知道你们在掩盖事实 稍等一下 人们 每个人...
the people have a right to know the truth as well.
都是有权力知道事情真相的
The truth is there's a deep, dark pond off route 9.
真相就是9号公路旁边有个深不见底的池塘
Nobody goes there. Your buddy's not here. Why don't we see if you can swim, huh?
没人去过那里 你哥们不在这儿 要不咱们去试试看你会不会游泳 你觉得怎样?
Hey, hey, you know you're not getting in there, right?
你可不想进去的吧?
Yeah. And at this point, I don't care.
对 不过反正现在这样 我也不在乎
You know why? Because we have the footage.
知道为什么吗? 因为我们有录像
We have real, actual footage of a supernatural monster.
我们有超自然怪物的录像 真的录像
And you know what else?
你知道还有什么吗?
And...
还有...
You are really gonna love this.
你们一定会喜欢这个的
We have recordings of conversations among Haven law enforcement discussing a conspiracy to cover it up.
我们录下了港湾警方密谋掩盖事实的对话
Can you believe that?
谁能相信这种事情呢?
So what I'm proposing is this... we form kind of like a partnership?
所以以下是我的建议 咱们搭档呗?
You let us tag around on the case. We get enough footage to finish the episode,
你让我们跟拍这个案子 等我们拍到足够的录像来结束这一集
and then this little illegal conversation of yours...
那你们之间的这点违法的对话...
it just accidentally gets left on the cutting room floor.
就会不小心留在剪辑室里了
Here's my offer.
以下是我的提议
We take your equipment, put it on the ground, and you watch, politely,
我们拿走你们的仪器 放在地上 当我砸烂它的每一片的时候
as I smash every piece of it.
你要老老实实有礼貌地看
From there, we grab your buddy on the way to the edge of town,
然后我们在送你出镇的路上把你哥们一接
and we light your van on fire.
之后再一把火烧了你们的车
And if you don't like that plan, I can always leave you inside the van. Deal?
你要不喜欢这个提议 那我烧车的时候 你也坐上去好了 如何?
Go ahead. Smash my stuff.
来呀 砸我东西呗
And anyways, it doesn't matter because all of our footage
随便你 反正我们所有的录像
is just automatically uploaded onto a secure server on the cloud.
都已经自动上传到一个安全的云服务器里了
So, sorry, buddy.
所以 抱歉啦哥们
- Dwight, just calm down. - Okay, I'm good.
- Dwight 别激动 - 没事 我没生气
- What? - I'm done pissing him off.
- 啊? - 我惹他生气了 就行了
I was just trying to get under his skin so that he'd slip up and let us know where they're uploading their footage.
我只是想惹怒他 这样他就会多嘴 告诉我们他们把录像上传到哪里去了
I can have Jennifer digging through those files by the time we get to the station.
等到警局以后 我可以让Jennifer找找那些文件
Jennifer can do that?
Jennifer还能干这个呢?
As far as I can tell, everyone younger than me can do that.
据我所知 比我年轻的都能呢
How's she doing?
她怎么样了?
Still in surgery. She's through the rough patch.
还在手术 情况很危险 但她挺过来了
How are you doing?
你怎么样?
Right.
哦
Fine.
挺好
Look, I just... I don't know. Today it's a phantom bullet.
我只是...我不知道 这次是看不见的子弹
Before that, she was stuck in an alternate reality.
在那之前 她被困在平行宇宙里
Every day I wake up, I think, "today is gonna be the day that I'm gonna lose her. "
我每天早上醒来的时候 都会觉得 "我今天要失去她了吧"
But you Haven't lost her.
可你还没有失去她
Look, Nathan, she is tough as nails.
听我说 Nathan 她很坚强
More importantly, she has us.
更重要的是 她还有我们
She has you to protect her.
你会保护她
That's just it.
问题就在这儿
I don't know if I know how to protect her anymore.
我不知道怎样才能继续保护她
- What are you talking about? - I... William.
- 你说什么呢? - 我...William
Her and William.
她和William
How can I protect her against that?
我要怎么保护她不受这种事情的伤害?
- How can I compete with that? - Hey, let me explain something to you.
- 我怎么跟这种情况抗争? - 嘿 你听我好好跟你说
In case you've forgotten, she went into that barn.
以免你忘了 她可是走进了那个谷仓
She sacrificed herself for the one person that she loved most in this world.
她为了她在这世上最爱的人牺牲了自己
- Yeah. That's you, buddy. - William... he knows everything about her.
- 对了 就是你 兄弟 - William...了解关于她的一切
They have this connection.
他们是相连的
He doesn't know Audrey. You know Audrey.
他不了解Audrey 你了解Audrey
So can we please figure out what the hell is growing claws
所以我们能不能赶紧搞清楚
and howling at the moon here in Haven? Do something to help her.
港湾到底出了什么有利爪对月嚎叫的怪兽? 干点实事来帮她
Victims aren't random.
死者不是随机选的
Abby and jemma knew each other forever. They talked on the phone every day.
Abby和Jemma从小一起长大 她俩天天煲电话粥
What about this other guy... Hank?
另一名死者Hank呢?
- How does... how does he fit in? - His birthday.
- 他又是怎么符合要求的? - 他的生日
Jemma said her and Abby were best friends since the day they were born, right?
Jemma说她和Abby自出生起就是好朋友 对吧?
So I looked into it.
所以我就查了一下
They were both born in Haven hospital on the same day... same day as Hank too.
她们是在同一天出生在港湾医院的 Hank也是那天出生的
- What day? - June 12, 1981.
- 哪天? - 1981年6月12日
June '81.
81年6月
- When The Troubles started up last time. - Call Haven hospital.
- 那是上一次异能出现的时候 - 联系港湾医院
See if anyone else was born on that day.
看看还有谁是那天出生的
Hopefully we can get to them before our trouble person.
希望我们能赶在异能者之前找到他们
We just celebrated Jennifer's birthday... June 12th.
我们刚给Jennifer过完生日 也是6月12日
- Where is she? - Haven herald.
- 她在哪里? - 港湾先驱报社
Let's go.
快走
Jennifer!
Jennifer!
Duke.
Duke
- duke, - Would you stop saying my name and just help me?
- Duke - 你能别瞎喊了么? 过来搭把手吧
Just calm down, okay? We've looked around.
冷静下来 我们查看过四周了
There is no blood here, which means either...
这里没有血迹 也就是说
Either Jennifer wasn't here, or she got away.
Jennifer要么不在这里 要么是逃走了
I found some more of that weird saliva stuff
我又找到了一些Gloria在尸体上发现的
Gloria collected from the other bodies, but no blood yet.
那些奇怪的疑似唾液的东西 但没看到有血迹
That thing... it hasn't taken any of its other targets.
那东西从来没绑架过它的目标
It killed them right on the spot, so we got to believe that Jennifer's okay.
它都是当场就把人杀了 所以我们得相信Jennifer没出事
This is her phone.
这是她的手机
- We have no way of contacting her now. - We'll find her.
- 我们现在联系不到她了 - 我们会找到她的
What if this thing is still after her?
万一这东西还在追杀她怎么办?
We don't know anything about it, Nathan.
我们完全不了解它 Nathan
I think we need to reconsider our deal with The Darkside Seekers.
我觉得我们最好重新考虑一下 暗黑寻鬼者提出的交易
You made a deal with those little weasels?
你跟那两个猥琐男做交易了?
No, not yet, but they have footage of this thing. Maybe it'll help us find it.
没 还没有 但他们手里有那东西的录像 也许能帮我们找到它
Or the Troubled person who's causing all of this.
或者找到造成这一切的异能者
You're only coming if you can keep it together.
你要能控制住情绪才可以跟来
If anything happens to her, I'm gonna kill somebody.
如果她出什么事 我一定会杀人的
I'm just trying to figure out if this is intentional sabotage
我就想知道你丫到底是故意的
or just sheer incompetence on your part,
还就只是单纯的无能
but either way, you have ruined the best piece of supernatural footage we have ever shot.
总之你是毁了我们拍过的最棒的超自然录像
Yeah, I feel like if I didn't have to cobble together all the equipment down in your basement,
我怎么觉得要是咱这仪器 不是我从你家地下室里拼凑出来的
- then maybe we wouldn't... - Oh, oh, really?
- 我们的录像可能也不会... - 哦你不是吧?
That's where we're gonna go?
非要往这事上扯?
- Sweet van, guys. - Great.
- 车不错啊 两位 - 好极了
What, you didn't want to spring for the airbrushed unicorn?
怎么没想着在上面画个独角兽什么的?
Which one of you g. I. Joes gets to threaten us today?
今天轮到哪位大兵威胁我们啊?
- that would be me. - Actually, we're just here to talk about our deal.
- 我 - 其实我们是来谈谈那个交易的
Show us what you got.
把你们拍的东西拿来看看
If it helps with the investigation, then maybe we can schedule a ride-along.
如果对调查有帮助 也许我们会考虑带你们一起办案
There's something wrong with our footage.
录像出了点问题
It's corrupted. It looks... Like, grainy and pixilated. It looks fake.
被破坏了 看着就像模糊的小点 看起来像是假造的
You think we're gonna buy that?
你以为我们会信?
Look, we all saw the creature.
我们都亲眼看到那个怪兽了
Don't try to tell us it's not real.
你可别说它不是真的
Nobody's saying it's not real, all right?
没说它不是真的好吗?
It's real. It's just the footage that this genius shot... we go live with that,
是真的啊 只不过这个天才拍的东西... 万一我们把这种东西播出去
we lose what little credibility we've got
我们的信誉就全没了
Do I look like I care about your credibility?
你觉得我像是在乎你们信誉的人吗?
Look, I'm just saying our monster looks like a million little black pixels, okay?
我只是想说 这个怪物看起来就像 几百万个像素拼出来的东西
- It's just worthless footage. - Play it anyways.
- 这视频一点价值都没有 - 不管怎样你都放一下
Yeah, great. Show them. Take a look. Be my guest.
行 好极了 给他们看 随便看 别客气
See, when you zoom in, it just looks like little black pixels,
你看 放大的时候 看起来就像是小黑点
like we just pasted the damn thing on there.
跟我们贴上去的一样
Give us a sec.
失陪一下
- Yeah. Take all day, guys. - Nice shot.
- 行啊 你们自便 - 拍得真好
Those black orbs, whatever the hell they are..
那些不知道是啥东西的黑色小球
that's what William used to turn us against each other.
是William用来让我们反目的东西
And Audrey said William controls the orbs, been using them with Troubled people.
Audrey说William控制这些东西 把它们用在异能者身上
So William's behind this. He created that thing.
所以这事的黑手是William 他创造了这个怪物
So there's no actual Troubled person.
所以根本没有异能者参与
But why is William after Jennifer and all those people born in '81?
可William为什么追杀Jennifer 还有其他81年出生的人呢?
- Let's go to the hospital and ask him. - He's still unconscious.
- 我们去医院问问他 - 他还在昏迷中
I guess I'm gonna have to wake him up long enough to beat some answers out of him.
我猜我只好让他多醒一会儿 好让我拷问一些答案出来
You stick with them and see what else they got.
你跟他俩待在一起 看他们还拍到了什么
what
什么情况
William... He's gone.
William...不见了
- I'm telling you, I feel fine. - That's impossible.
- 我跟你说 我好好的 - 这不可能
No, the doctor... he can't explain it either.
是不可能 医生也说不清楚
He says that all my internal stitches from the surgery are gone.
他说手术在我体内留下的针线痕迹都没了
It's like I was never injured at all.
就像我从没受过伤一样
But if you're healed, does that mean...?
如果你痊愈了 那是不是意味着...
William is too.
William也痊愈了
Stan, how you doing?
Stan 你还好吗?
It was time to change his I.V. Bag.
当时正要给他换输液袋
When I unlocked the door, these two guys kicked it open and knocked me out...
我刚把门打开 那俩家伙就冲了进来 把我打昏...
- Stan, don't... don't worry about it, okay? -  I'm really sorry, guys.
- Stan 别担心 好吗? - 真的很抱歉
There isn't anything you could've done.
你当时也无能为力
The guys Stan saw...
Stan看见的人...
one of them sounds a whole lot like your friend from the barn, the big one.
其中一个很像你从谷仓来的朋友 大个子那个
- He just carried William out? - One of the cops who got attacked outside...
- 他把William扛出去了? - 外面一个被袭击的警察
he swears that William walked out of here on his own two feet,
他发誓William是自己走出去的
healed, just like Audrey.
痊愈了 就跟Audrey一样
Hello?
喂?
Jennifer? Is that you? Jennifer, where are you?
Jennifer? 是你吗? Jennifer 你在哪?
- Duke? - Jennifer?
- Duke? - Jennifer?
Duke, I left my cell at the herald.
Duke 我把手机落在报社了
Vince and I saw a monster.
Vince和我看见了一个怪物
- You're with Vince? - No, no
- 你跟Vince在一起? - 没有 没有
Vince went to the archives to see if he could figure out what this thing was,
Vince去翻资料了 想查查这东西是什么
but, Duke, it was huge, and the teeth... it was horrible.
Duke 它超级大 有牙 特别吓人
- Jennifer... - I was just digging through some files like you asked me,
- Jennifer... - 我当时正在找文件
and then all of a sudden, it's like I knew something was coming for me,
然后突然一下 就像我知道有东西在追杀我一样
like that "eerie eyes watching you from behind" feeling.
那种"有可怕的眼睛在你背后盯着你"的感觉
- And then there it was outside like it was sniffing me out. -  Jennifer, where are you?
- 然后它就出现了 好像在嗅我的味道 - Jennifer 你在哪?
At an empty warehouse that Dave and Vince own at the end of canaan street.
Canaan街尽头的一个空仓库里 Dave和Vince的房产
Vince said that nobody knows about it and that I'd be safe here, but why is that thing after me?
Vince说没人知道这个地方 我会很安全 可那玩意为什么会追杀我?
I want you to stay put. We'll be right there.
你老实待在那里 我们马上就到
- Duke, I'm really scared. - I know. Just sit tight.
- Duke 我好害怕 - 我知道 待在那里
Tell her we need a description. Still Haven't got a good look at this thing.
问问她那东西长什么样 我们对它还没有一个清晰的印象
Look, Jennifer, I want you to write down everything that you saw.
Jennifer 把你看见的东西都写下来
We're on our way.
我们马上就到
Hey, I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
我不会让你出事的
Write it down, like I could ever scrub that image from my mind.
还写下来 好像我能忘得了那种东西似的
unstake my heart
卸掉你的心
gloria:rougarou not human.transdimensional trouble? good luck!
Gloria: 食肉怪不是人类 也许是跨时空的异能? 好运!
All this, uh, jury-rigged equipment you haul around...
你们这些临时装配的仪器
have you found anything in Haven with it?
在港湾有没有发现什么东西?
Yeah, we've had a few beeps, but nothing I can officially confirm... why?
有 当时响过几次 但我不知道是什么 怎么了?
I have a friend who's in some danger, and we got nothing.
我有个朋友遇到了危险 可我们什么线索都没有
Do you have, uh, anything in here that can help me with this?
你们这儿有没有能帮到我的东西?
What is that?
那是什么?
It's fluid from the victim's blood, but first we run some tests.
是从死者身上找到的血液 但我们得先做几个测试
And then we get the scoop?
独家新闻归我们?
Okay.
好吧
All right, fine.
挺好
Just give me a few moments to warm up the cells,
给我几分钟预热一下这些仪器
and you have got yourself a deal.
然后咱们就算是说定了
What's up with this obsession?
你怎么就这么痴迷于搞这种事情?
I mean, right now most people... they'd be running for the hills.
现如今大部分人都当背包客去了吧
Well, to tell you the truth, it's not my first time in Haven.
说实话 其实这不是我头一回来港湾
I used to summer here with my family when I was a kid.
我小时候会跟家人一起来这里过暑假
And you saw something?
你看见奇怪的东西了?
It was summer, 1983.
那是1983年的夏天
We were all out at the beach.
我们都去海滩玩了
I was playing down by the water with some local kid.
我当时正跟当地一个小孩潜水玩
All of a sudden, this man just comes up out of the ocean.
突然 有个人就这么从海里走了出来
He walks right towards us.
他直直地走向我们
He grabs my friend, and then he just pulls him back out into the waves.
抓住了我的朋友 然后把他扯进了水里
I was so scared, I- I couldn't even yell for help.
我吓坏了 连大声呼救都做不到
I sat there for an hour just staring out into the surf.
我傻坐在那儿一小时 盯着海浪看
He never came back up.
他再也没出来
Neither did the kid.
那个孩子也没有
I should've done something.
我当时应该做些什么的
Ever since then, I have spent my life trying to find something,
从那以后 我就把所有的精力 都放在寻找证据上
anything that might explain what I saw that summer.
希望找到哪怕一丁点证据 能解释我那个夏天看到的东西
And when I read that story about the heartless corpse,
当我看到那些无心尸体的报道以后
I knew I had to come back out here.
我就知道我得回来
I had to find the truth.
我得找到真相
Well, saved by the bell.
哎呀 铃声解救我于水火啊
All right, equipment's ready.
好了 仪器准备好了
- you? - Sure.
- 你呢? - 当然
Spectral imaging.
光谱成像
That is a no.
啥也没有
E.M.F. Gauge... Nada.
EMF计数...也没有
Geiger counter... Come on.
盖革计数器 来吧
No, it's still nothing.
不行 还是啥都没
Damn.
靠
All right, let's try something different.
好吧 来试试别的东西
I built this little baby myself.
这小宝贝儿是我自己组装的
I call it an electrical polarity guide, an e. P.G.
我叫它电极指南 EPG
It's a modified cathode. It monitors inverse charges in the molecular field.
这是改装后的负极板 能在分子领域监控反转电极
Let's see.
来看看吧
Show daddy what you can do.
让老爸看看你能干嘛
I mean... I mean, look, it may not look like much, but I know what I'm doing... trust me.
虽说我看着不靠谱 可我知道我在做什么 相信我
Okay, so this thing can tell us when the rougarou is close?
也就是说这东西能告诉我们食肉怪是不是在附近?
Yeah, I guess so, theoretically.
应该是吧 理论上讲是的
I told you.
告诉你了吧
Duke?
Duke?
Okay, I'll be right there.
好的 我马上就到
Okay, I need that machine.
我需要你的仪器
Ahah, well, you know, this is a patent-protected device.
那可不行 这是专利产品
Let's just go.
赶紧走吧
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 走吗? - 走啊
I don't understand. What does William want with me?
我不懂 William为什么想要我?
June 12, 1981... is that your birthday, right?
你的生日是1981年6月12日 对吧?
William's been going after everyone born on that day.
William在追杀那天出生的每一个人
That was the day The Troubles came back during the last cycle.
刚好是异能上一次回来的那天
We know it has something to do with Jennifer's connection to the barn.
肯定跟Jennifer和谷仓的联系有关
- Why'd you bring them? - No choice.
- 带他们来干什么啊? - 我别无选择
They got some gadget that can help us locate the rougarou.
他们有仪器能帮我们确定食肉怪的位置
- It measures the polarity of a... Something. - Yeah, thank you.
- 测电极还是什么的东西 - 是的 谢谢
Basically this is a monitoring device that I built that, um...
这是我装的一个监控仪器
Yeah, it's a box, tells you when the monster's close.
好吧 就是个盒子 能告诉我们怪物是否在附近
Turn it on, the gauge moves in this direction, then that means that...
把它打开 如果计量器指示这个方向 就说明...
It's close.
它就在附近
guys?
同志们?
- No gun. - Sorry.
- 别开枪 - 抱歉
I don't think bullets would take this thing down anyway, not if William's behind it.
反正如果William是幕后指使的话 我觉得子弹也不能伤到这玩意
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
等等 等等
I... I lost the signal.
没...没信号了
I don't know. Maybe it's moved on.
我也不知道 也许是它走了
Well, then what are we waiting for? Let's get out of here.
那我们还等什么? 赶紧走啊
- Okay, it's making a different sound... why? - I don't know.
- 它现在冒别的怪声了 啥情况? - 我也不知道啊
It's definitely not the rougarou.
绝对不是食肉怪
Whatever this is, it's giving off the exact opposite reading.
不管它是什么 读数正好跟食肉怪相反
- It's coming from you. - What?
- 是你这儿出来的 - 啥?
Are you serious? First some monster wants to eat my heart out,
可不可笑啊 先是有怪物要吃我的心
- and now I'm some kind of paranormal phenomenon? - Jennifer, where'd you get that book?
- 结果现在连我都成了超自然现象了? - Jennifer 那本书你从哪里拿的?
This was just in a box of old junk that my birth parents left behind.
这是我亲生父母留下的盒子里翻出来的垃圾
No, that's not junk.
这才不是垃圾呢
Seriously, I've read this, and it makes twilight look like faulkner.
真的 我读过这本书 用福克纳风格写暮光之城的感觉
No, I-I gave that to agent Howard before I came to Haven.
不是 这是我来港湾之前给Howard探员的书
If you found that at your birth parents' house, that means...
如果你在你亲生父母家里找到的 那意味着...
Wait, he must have wanted her to find it.
等等 他肯定希望她找到这本书
That's not just some cheesy paperback.
这可不是什么俗气的平装书
It's something more.
它意义不止如此
Okay. Now what?
好吧 现在又怎样了?
I don't want the magic beeping book.
我才不想要这个神奇乱哔魔法书
- You should keep it. - Please, Jennifer.
- 你拿着吧 - 拜托 Jennifer
Agent Howard is somehow linked to this barn and now this book and now you.
Howard探员和谷仓有某种联系 现在又出现了你 还有这本书
Guys, we should go.
同志们 我们得走了
So it's me and the book together. That's just perfect.
所以是我加这本书才有这效果 好极了简直
- Everyone stay together! - Again with the lights?
- 大家都聚在一起! - 又把灯弄没了?
Anderson, give me that camera. Use the other one. You up?
Anderson 把摄像机给我 用另一个 准备好了吗?
- Yeah. - Keep rolling.
- 嗯 - 接着拍
- Yeah, I'm rolling.
- 拍着呢
Heads up, heads up! Get Jennifer out of here!
抬头 抬头! 把Jennifer带出去!
- This way! - Over here.
- 这边! - 走这边
- Oh, God. Is he okay? - Yeah, he's all right.
- 老天 他没事吧? - 她没事
Anderson, go with them. I'll distract it.
Anderson 跟他们一起走 我来引开它
- Go, go. - Over here!
- 走 快走 - 这边!
- You sure? - He's all right. He's just out cold.
- 你确定他没事? - 没事 只是昏死过去了
It doesn't want him. It wants Jennifer.
它不想要他 只想要Jennifer
Hey, you overgrown fur ball, over here!
喂 你个长过头的大毛球 看这边!
Come on, we got to help Duke get it away from her.
走吧 我们得帮Duke引开它
Come on! Come on, come get me!
来啊! 来啊 来抓我!
Listen, we're gonna get you out of here, okay?
我们会带你出去的 好吗?
Okay, yeah, you might, but that thing's trying to eat me!
你是肯定没事 可那玩意想吃我啊!
No, we're not gonna let it.
我们不会让它得逞的
See, there seems to be some kind of connection between you and the book.
你和那本书之间似乎有什么联系
Okay, maybe those readings... maybe they'll help us find a way to stop it.
那些读数可能会帮我们想办法阻止它
Can we please talk a little quieter?
咱们说话能小声点么?
I can't run with a camera!
我带着摄像机跑不动啊!
Come on! Come on!
快点! 快点!
Move, move! It's right behind me!
赶紧走! 它就在我后面!
- Come on, let's go! - I'm coming!
- 快 咱们走! - 我来了!
this way!
这边!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
来啊傻大个儿!
Come on! Wait, wait, where is he?
来啊! 等等 他人呢?
Seth, let's go. Move it.
Seth 快走 赶紧的
Where... where is it? Where is the book?
在哪里? 那本书在哪里?
- Oh, my God, I dropped it. - It's over there.
- 天哪 我给掉了 - 在那边
We need that book.
我们需要那本书
Okay.
好吧
Wait a minute.
等一下
You can do this.
你可以的
Okay, all right.
好吧 好吧
- Hey, hey. - Jennifer!
- 嘿 - Jennifer!
Get back here. Get back here.
快回来 快回来
Get the damn book!
快拿到那本书!
- What just happened? - Where'd it go?
- 什么情况? - 它去哪了?
Jennifer!
Jennifer!
Jennifer?
Jennifer?
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧? - 没事
What?
怎么了?
How's Dwight? Is he gonna be okay?
Dwight怎么样了? 他会没事吧?
Oh, so it's "Dwight" now? Not "Bigfoot"?
都叫上名字啦 不叫人大脚怪了?
I'm serious. How is he?
我没开玩笑 他没事吧?
Paramedics said he'll be fine.
医生说他会没事的
It's just a mild concussion.
轻微脑震荡而已
What the hell happened in there, huh?
那里到底是怎么回事?
Maybe the opposing frequencies created a compressed static field,
可能是相对频率产生了一个压缩静态场
and... I don't know... poof maybe?
然后...我也不知道...证据吧?
- I'm sure that's what happened. - Well, that's reassuring.
- 肯定就是这么回事 - 松了一口气啊
What you did in there for Jennifer, if you hadn't...
你救了Jennifer 如果不是你...
okay, let's not make a big deal out of this, detective.
行了 别把这个太当回事了 警探
I don't think I'm quite ready to start being praised by the men in black.
我还没准备好被黑衣人嘉奖呢
So where you off to next... loch ness, Atlantis?
你们下一站打算找什么? 尼斯湖水怪还是亚特兰蒂斯?
Oh, come on, you don't really believe in that stuff, do you?
哎呀 你该不是真信那种东西吧?
Don't encourage him, Nathan.
你别鼓励他 Nathan
Between the footage they gathered and all the information Dwight so foolishly leaked,
有了他们的录像和Dwight这个白痴泄露的信息
- it'll take every trick we have in the book... - okay, don't give yourself a heart attack there, cronkite.
- 我们得费多大劲才能... - 行啦 别自己吓自己了 大记者
We are not going to be releasing the footage, not ever.
我们永远都不会发表这个录像的
Why not?
为什么不?
Well, even though you and your brother are sloppy, you're uncreative,
尽管你和你兄弟既粗心又没创意
you have utterly laughable passwords, what you do for this town
电脑密码简直要笑破人肚皮 可你们为这个小镇做的事情
is really important.
真的很重要
What all of you do is.
你们都是
- These people... they didn't ask to be, you know... - Troubled.
- 这些人 他们也不想要这些... - 异能
Exactly.
是的
They just are, and turning a group of innocent people
他们只是天生如此 把这群无辜的人
into a sideshow attraction, it's not exactly why I set out on this search.
变成引人注目的节目 不是我做这项研究的初衷
I found out the truth.
我找到了真相
That's enough.
这就够了
Anyway...
总之...
Hey, your cameraman, Anderson... is he on board too?
你的摄像师Anderson也这么想吗?
Well, he's still trying to wrap his head around it,
他现在脑子还糊涂着呢
but knowing him, yeah, he'll feel the same way.
不过我了解他 他跟我想法一样
Good luck.
祝你们好运
Keep that luck for yourself. You're the one who's gonna need it.
自己留着吧 你们才是需要好运的人
So is this your first time destroying a supernatural monster with a magical book?
这是你第一次用魔法书打败一个超自然怪兽?
Yeah.
对
How do you feel about dating Hermione?
女朋友变赫敏的感觉如何?
Well, you know, we all have our stuff.
嗯 咱们都有自己头疼的事儿
I snore when I drink red wine.
我一喝红酒就打鼾
Yes, you do, very loudly.
没错 还挺大声的
Very loudly.
特别大
How are you holding up?
你还好吧?
All things considered, I'm fine, but, yeah, still confused.
总的来看 我挺好 不过我还是很困惑
This book... you guys seriously can't see the guard symbol?
这本书 你们是真的看不到守卫者的标记吗?
It's orange. It's glowing.
橙色的 发光呢
How can you guys not see this?
你们怎么能看不到呢?
It's meant just for you.
这是专门为你准备的
That's why even I can't see it.
所以才连我都看不到
- Maybe it's a message from agent Howard. - What does it mean?
- 也许是Howard探员留下的讯息 - 什么意思?
Why is a guard symbol on the cover of that book?
守卫者的标记怎么会在这本书的封皮上?
Nathan...
Nathan...
You still feeling okay?
你感觉还好吧?
A couple hours ago, you had a hole right through you.
几小时前 你身上还有个弹孔呢
Physically I feel great.
身体感觉很好
But then again, that probably means William does too.
但同样的 这意味着William也痊愈了
He killed innocent people and made it look like a trouble all just to get to Jennifer.
他杀了无辜的人 弄成异能的样子 全都是为了找到Jennifer
Hey, guys, come here.
同志们 快过来
I found something. I think it's like a riddle.
我找到了点东西 好像是个谜语
I just opened the book, and it started glowing.
我刚把书打开 它就开始发光了
"In times of great evil, the child of ruin
"大恶魔出现的时候 毁灭之子
must find the heart of Haven and summon the door. "
必须找到港湾的心脏并召唤出门"
Sounds like a creepy zeppelin lyric.
好诡异 像齐柏林飞船的歌词
What's a child of ruin?
毁灭之子是什么?
I think it's me.
好像是我
That's why William wants you dead, because...
难怪William想要你的命 因为...
because I can summon the door.
因为我能召唤出门
And send William through it.
把William送过去
To where?
送去哪?
To wherever he came from.
他来的地方
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入